Now,
9.prepare phase 2
some prices are empty(rs.1)
fix nightly exports and dashboad price update.
check if seat llocation part works fine. check master data from phase 1 as well-check the flow and data quality
district aid FR - not removing raised records. showing all everytimed showing summed up instead of seperate unlike public and district. 
let add article item be on respective page itself

Before Event,
10.Sanity check - before Master data download
    1. check if the district data is changed using python - overall vs item count
    2. check all other exports and values
    3. check dashboad values against master data values.
    4. check imcomplete cells
    5. check order management data with and without split matches

After Event,
1. backup migration files from supabase
2. Use .dev account or maruvoorhelp account. Forward mails to maruvoorhelp and add as recovery and phone number
3. Submit all files, Code to Drive





